A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014) FA760
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2014.068: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2014; AC_2014_068; 8.72 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R4437-R4442, and one large flat file
  - CIF, 2008-2014; AC_2014_068_3; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 CIF 301 - NONPROFIT FINANCE FUND - FINANCIAL CAPACITY OF SELECT NYC CULTURAL INNOVATION FUND APPLICANTS AND GRANTEES, 2008-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 303 - CASITA MARIA - PUBLIC ART PROJECTS, 2011-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 304 - CEC ARTSLINK - ONE BIG CITY, 2011-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 305 - CENTER FOR URBAN PEDAGOGY - SOCIAL JUSTICE DESIGN CLINIC, 2011-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 306 - GROUNDSWELL COMMUNITY MURAL PROJECT - SHAPING STREETSCAPES, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 308 - EL PUENTE DE WILLIAMSSBURG - CULTURAL NEEDS ASSESSMENT, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 309 - PERFORMANCE ZONE - ONLINE BARTER NETWORK FOR ARTISTS, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 310 - GREENPOINT MANUFACTURING AND DESIGN CENTER LOCAL DEVELOPMENT CORP - NATURALLY OCCURRING CULTURAL DISTRICTS WORKING GROUP, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 311 - MISNOMER - INNOVATIVE FUNDRAISING MARKETING, 2011-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 312 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF LATINO INDEPENDENT PRODUCERS - LATINO ARTIST MENTORING PROJECT, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 313 - WILDLIFE CONSERVATION SOCIETY - CLIMATE RESILIENT DESIGNS FOR MANHATTAN, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 314 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - BROADWAY 1000 STEPS, 2010-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CIF 316 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - ACTIVATING TRANSNATIONAL PERFORMANCE IN NEW YORK CITY, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
  - Climate Change (CLI), 2009-2014; AC_2014_068_4; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2009 CLI 322 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION PROGRAMS, 2009-2013 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 CLI 323 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION PROGRAMS FOR AGRICULTURE RESEARCH INSTITUTION, 2009-2013 (Box R4437)
    - 2010 CLI 312 - UNIVERSITY OF DAR ES SALAAM (TANZANIA) - TRAINING ON CLIMATE CHANGE ADAPTATION, 2010-2014 (Box R4438)
    - 2010 CLI 325 - INSTITUTE FOR SOCIAL AND ENVIRONMENTAL TRANSITION - QUY NHON HYDROLOGY AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT MODELLING, 2010-2013 (Box R4438)
    - 2011 CLI 307 - SOCIETY FOR PARTICIPATORY RESEARCH IN ASIA (INDIA) - STRENGTHEN CIVIL SOCIETY ENGAGEMENT WITH URBAN POLICY, 2011-2013 (Box R4440)
  - RES, 2009-2014; AC_2014_068_5; 4.78 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes and 1 large flat file folder
    - 2009 RES 305 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP LP - TECHNOLOGY TRENDS IN INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 2009-2010 (Box R4437)
    - 2009 RES 305 - Scenarios on the Future of Technology and International Development - Oversize, 2009-2010; 2014:068:001 (Folder 1)
    - 2010 RES 312 - BERTELSMANN FOUNDATION, NORTH AMERICA - MEGATRENDS IN GLOBAL INTERACTION PROJECT, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 RES 312 - Megatrends in Global Interaction - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:010 (Box R4439)
    - 2011 RES 302 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF SINGAPORE - TREND MONITORING AND HORIZON SCANNING IN ASIA, 2009-2014 (Box R4442)
  - THS, 2009-2014; AC_2014_068_6; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2009 THS 338 - MINISTRY OF HEALTH, RWANDA - NATIONAL eHEALTH INFORMATION SYSTEM, 2009-2014 (Box R4438)
    - 2010 THS 308 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR GLOBAL HEALTH AND SOCIAL TRANSFORMATION (UGANDA) - MINISTERIAL HEALTH SYSTEMS, 2010-2013 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 THS 322 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH, BANGLADESH - THE LANCET SERIES ON BANGLADESH, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 THS 326 - HANOI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (VIETNAM) - HEALTH SYSTEMS RESEARCH CENTER, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 THS 330 - ASIA FOUNDATION - MAPPING HEALTH MARKET INNOVATIONS IN PAKISTAN, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
    - 2010 THS 349 - CLINTON HEALTH ACCESS INITIATIVE - KENYA HEALTH SECTOR ANNUAL OPERATING PLAN, 2010-2014 (Box R4439)
  - Campaign for American Workers (CAW), 2010-2014; AC_2014_068_7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 CAW 310 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - PATIENT PROTECTION AND AFFORDABLE HEALTH CARE ACT RESEARCH, 2010-2014 (Box R4438)
  - DSN, 2010-2014; AC_2014_068_8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 DSN 311 - WILDLIFE CONSERVATION SOCIETY - ONE HEALTH ACTION IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 2010-2014 (Box R4438)
  - EVA, 2010-2014; AC_2014_068_9; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 EVA 308 - CLAREMONT GRADUATE UNIVERSITY - DISSEMINATION OF BEST PRACTICES IN ASIA AND AFRICA, 2010-2014 (Box R4438)
    - 2010 EVA 308 - Emerging Practices in International Development Evaluation (2 copies) - Published Material, 2010-2014; 2014:068:008, 2014:068:009 (Box R4438)
  - INV, 2010-2013; AC_2014_068_11; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 INV 311 - PENNSYLVANIA TREASURY DEPARTMENT - FINANCING MODELS FOR ENERGY EFFICIENCY RETROFITS, 2010-2013 (Box R4438)
    - 2011 INV 305 - SERVICE EMPLOYEES INTERNATIONAL UNION - HEALTHCARE DEVELOPMENT FINANCIAL INSTITUTION, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 INV 309 - FUNDACAO INTERUNIVERSITARIA DE ESTUDOS E PESQUISAS SOBRE O TRABALHO (BRAZIL) -IMPACT INVESTMENT IN THE SOLIDARITY ECONOMY, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 INV 310 - GREATERCAPITAL (SOUTH AFRICA) - IMPACT INVESTING POLICY RESEARCH, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
  - OAF, 2010-2014; AC_2014_068_12; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2010 OAF 305 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA - CANOPY CONSTRUCTION FOR OUTDOOR AMPHITHEATRE, 2010-2013 (Box R4438)
    - 2011 OAF 301 - KENYA DIABETES MANAGEMENT AND INFORMATION CENTER - INCREASE DIABETES AWARENESS, 2011-2014 (Box R4441)
  - TRA, 2010-2012; AC_2014_068_13; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2010 TRA 327 - OPEN PLANNING PROJECT - EVENTS ON TRANSPORTATION TECHNOLOGIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4439)
  - CAC, 2008-2014; AC_2014_068_14; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 CAC 309 - OVE ARUP PARTNERS INTERNATIONAL LIMITED (ENGLAND) - ASIA CLIMATE CHANGE INITIATIVE, 2008-2013 (Box R4439)
    - 2011 CAC 312 - CHALLENGE TO CHANGE (UNITED KINGDOM) - ACCCRN - YOUTH INITIATIVES IN VIETNAM, 2011-2014 (Box R4440)
    - 2011 CAC 313 - MERCY CORPS - ACCCRN - INDONESIAN CITIES PROJECT, 2009-2014 (Box R4440)
  - CRD, 2009-2013; AC_2014_068_15; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 CRD 304 - FOREST TRENDS - AFRICAN FOOD SECURITY CARBON FUND, 2009-2013 (Box R4440)
  - EIN, 2011-2014; AC_2014_068_16; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 EIN 313 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - URBAN RESEARCH INNOVATION AWARD, 2011-2014 (Box R4441)
  - OAS, 2011-2014; AC_2014_068_17; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 OAS 312 - IPS ASIA-PACIFIC CENTER FOUNDATION INC. (PHILIPPINES) - SUPPORT OF ACTIVITIES TO PROMOTE CRITICAL REPORTING ON CLIMATE CHANGE, 2011-2014 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OAS 312 - Linking Borders - Reportage from Our Mekong - Published Material, 2011-2014; 2014:068:019 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OAS 315 - ASIAN MIGRANT CENTRE (HONG KONG) - CLIMATE CHANGE AND MIGRATION IN THE GREATER MEKONG SUB-REGION, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OAS 315 - Migration in the Greater Mekong Subregion: Resource Book - Published Materials, 2011-2013; 2014:068:020 (Box R4441)
  - OPP, 2009-2014; AC_2014_068_18; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 OPP 301 - EMCARTS - NEW YORK CITY CULTURAL INNOVATION FUND, LESSONS LEARNED, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OPP 305 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST - NEW YORK ALLIANCE FOR CAREERS IN HEALTH CARE, 2011-2013 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OPP 311 - HERE ART CENTER - PORTRAIT OF A NEW YORK ARTIST VIDEO, 2009-2014 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OPP 315 - HEART OF BROOKLYN CULTURAL INSTITUTIONS - BUILDING STRONG COMMUNITY NETWORKS, 2011-2014 (Box R4441)
    - 2011 OPP 319 - MUSEUM FOR AFRICAN ART - SOCIAL AND POLITICAL HISTORY, 2011-2014 (Box R4441)
  - PHS, 1993-2014; AC_2014_068_19; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2011 PHS 312 - GRANTMAKERS IN THE ARTS - GENERAL OPERATING EXPENSES (3 FOLDERS), 1993-2003 (Box R4441, Box R4442)
    - 2011 PHS 314 - RESOURCE ALLIANCE LIMITED (ENGLAND) - THAILAND NGO AWARDS, 2011-2014 (Box R4442)
    - 2011 PHS 315 - NATIONAL COMMITTEE FOR RESPONSIVE PHILANTHROPY - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2008-2013 (Box R4442)
  - PRD, 2011-2014; AC_2014_068_21; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 PRD 205 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR LAW REPORTING - DIGITIZE RECORDS, 2011-2014 (Box R4442)
    - 2011 PRD 206 - EDWARD T. JACKSON AND ASSOCIATES LTD. (CANADA) - PRIDE EVALUATION MONITORING / DATA COLLECTION FOR DEMONSTRATIONS, 2011-2014 (Box R4442)
    - 2011 PRD 209 - NASSCOM FOUNDATION (INDIA) - SUB-CONTRACTING DEMONSTRATION, 2011-2014 (Box R4442)
    - 2011 PRD 212 - IT ENABLED SERVICES SECRETARIAT (GHANA) - IMPACT SOURCING - EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES, 2011-2013 (Box R4442)
  - PRE, 2011-2013; AC_2014_068_22; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2011 PRE 314 - WASHINGTON AREA WOMEN'S FOUNDATION - MEASURING RETURN ON INVESTMENT FOR WOMEN AND GIRLS, 2011-2013 (Box R4442)